4x09 - The Young and the Stoned
Subtitles: swsub.com
- I cannot find this place.
- Why are you too proud
to use your navigation system?
Ask yourself that.
I tried the navigation.
It can't find it either.
That's too bad 'cause you're about
to miss the day's last bit of sun.
Just tell me where to turn.
I'm on Poplar.
I don't know Poplar.
Head back down the Hill,
- I'll give you directions from sunset.
- I don't even know where the bottom is.
Why did we have
to move up here anyway?
'cause it's an insane house, that's why.
For 30 gs a month it should be.
Stop stressing about money.
Vince says if he never
makes another dollar
his advance check from Clouds
can keep us in this house for 16 months.
- 18 months.
That will stop me from stressing.
Okay, wait a second,
I think I'm heading back down right now.
- Durand drive... that sound familiar?
- Yeah, turn there.
- God damn it.
- What?
Some girl just ran into me.
Oh my god, I think it's Anna Faris.
- Really?
- You know what? Let me call you back.
What happened?
Anna Faris just smashed into E.
Sweet.
Did you not see me?
I am so sorry.
I got distracted for a second.
It's totally my fault.
Well, it's okay.
it was an accident.
Would you mind not coming any closer?
Why? You think I'm, like,
some kind of a crazy fan or something?
No no, it's just that
I'm in a towel.
I just got done with pilates
and I forgot a change.
And, you know, who wants to wear
sweaty clothes after a shower?
So you decided
to drive home in a towel?
- It's a little weird, huh?
- Not weird.
It's just not very practical
in case you got in an accident.
So what now?
Well, I guess I've got
to get your insurance, right?
I don't have my wallet.
Okay, you're just a mess today.
Yes. Yes,
but your fly is down.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry, I just wanted
to take some of the attention off me.
Look, I'm feeling a little exposed.
Can I give you my number?
I'm gonna be home
in, like, 10 minutes
and then I'll give you
everything you need.
Yeah, that's cool.
Let me get my phone
and get your number.
- I'm really sorry.
- That's okay.
It'll be all right.
What time's dinner, daddy?
As soon as I'm done
with this script, sweetie.
Oh my God,
That is so funny!
No, you are kidding me.
That is so funny.
Oh my god, too funny.
Will you shut up?
Okay then.
Yes, A.S.A.P.
Thank you so much.
Well, guess who that was.
Let me see, it was Cara Grossman
and she wants to know
if she should should get her eyebrows
waxed first or if you should.
It was my old producer from
The Young And The Restless.
What did he want?
- Me.
- I don't get it.
It's the 35th anniversary of Y&R
and they want me to reprise
my role as Kendall Scott.
Are you serious?
I am.
It seems that Kendall
still gets quite a bit of fan mail
and the writers were in a bind
and they've come up
with a little idea that
could work for tomorrow.
- I hope you told them no.
- I told them we'd talk about it.
We talked about it
so you tell them no.
We have not talked about it.
Honey, what is there to talk about?
I don't know...
tell me that it's exciting
and that if I did it, I'd be good.
It's a soap opera. There is no good,
there's just degrees of bad.
Well, then tell me
that I would be pretty,
as pretty as the day I left the show.
Well, you left the show
when you were 25
and now they shoot
everything in high def.
You are such an asshole!
- Come on, baby.
- Yeah, right. Well, ask anybody,
you've aged a lot worse
than I have, baby.
Come here, honey.
Where are you going?
- To call my producer...
- For what?
...and tell him Kendall Scott,
town slut, is back.
What's up, boys?
For a guy who just got
into an accident, you seem happy.
Maybe he's got a head injury.
It's a fender-bender.
I'm fine. Are you nuts?
I hope you didn't tell Ms. Faris that,
'cause we're gonna sue
the crap out of her.
We're not suing anybody.
there's barely any damage.
Yeah, visible damage,
but internal damage
is a whole other thing.
- Let it go, Drama.
- E, come on, what's up?
I don't know.
She's cute.
- That she is.
- We had a little moment.
- No shot.
- No way.
You're not a member
of the celeb club, bro.
- It'll never happen.
- I got her number.
I crashed into an 80-year-old woman
once. She gave me her number too.
Whatever.
I'm calling.
I bet my left nut
he could not close Anna Faris.
Gee, a bet I'd love to win.
Shit.
What happened?
She gave me the wrong number.
Don't feel too bad, E.
You're just a regular
person, a civilian.
Too bad she didn't hit me.
We'd be fucking by now.
- Good morning, Ari.
- Is that smirk for me
or are your ben wa balls shifting?
Just wondering how you're feeling
about not being the biggest
star in your house anymore.
Don't be a wiseass.
How did you know?
It's on defamer.
You're kidding.
Oh, Ari, be proud of her.
She's gonna light up the screen
and bring a newfound
excitement to Genoa city.
You watch that shit?
Y&R is fourth
on my Tivo season pass priority list.
I haven't missed an episode in 12 years.
- That is so sad.
- You should go down to the set today.
Watch your wife's work,
be supportive.
I got my own life's work
to support, Lloyd.
Who the hell is this?
That's the underage
student she seduces, Julio.
Not a great picture. I've a better one.
It's my screen saver, if you wanna see.
- Clear my schedule.
- Even your lunch?
I'm going to be eating
Julio's lunch today.
Hi, Julio.
- I got it.
- Got what?
Anna Faris's address.
Wait till she sees me
show up on her doorstep.
What? I should pay for the car?
Is this really about the money
or is this about your little moment?
- We did have a moment.
- She's an actress.
- So what, I'm an idiot?
- No, she's a good actress.
Is E still bitching about
being bitch-slapped by a bitch?
He's rightfully upset.
Well, let it go.
We have bigger problems.
What's that Turtle?
Pink dot insisting on seeing a note
before you use
Vince's credit card again?
- Tey discontinued his favorite weed.
- O favorite weed,
and it's not discontinued,
it's extinct, gone forever.
Like the Yangtze river dolphin.
I gotta wait for the cable guy.
How am I gonna do that with no weed?
Why don't you pick up one
of the 50 kinds of weed
- you've been living off for 20 years?
- I'm too distraught.
What if I was to tell you
that I have a secret stash
of the most-recently-extinct
aurora borealis
in a box in the living room?
I would say if I wasn't
worried about appearances,
I would kiss you right now.
How much you got?
Enough to make
waiting for the cable guy tolerable.
Fantastic.
You know what?
Maybe I'll stick around,
cook us a nice lunchtime feast.
You do the shopping.
If I pick the menu.
Done.
You in, E?
I can't. Got too much stuff to do today.
I'll see you guys later.
What's he gotta do?
I really miss this lovely canvas.
Well, I hope
I don't disappoint, Steven.
It's really nerve-wracking
when you haven't been in front
of the camera for so long.
Don't worry. You look as good as ever
and you will be fantastic.
Surprise, honey.
Your husband has arrived.
Ari, what are you doing here?
Well, I wanted to see your work.
I wanted to be the supportive
husband and meet your colleagues.
How are you?
Ari gold. Nice to meet you.
I am the man behind
this beautiful woman.
Your wife has
the most amazing skin.
She does, doesn't she?
Do you think you could give
us just a couple seconds?
Sure.
Whatever you need.
- What are you doing here?
- I heard about your scene.
Come on, it's a soap.
What did you think I was gonna be doing?
I don't know,
discovering that your husband
is really
your long-lost tranny cousin?
Who gives a shit?
All I know is
I don't want another
man's lips on my wife.
- It's barely a kiss.
- And how are your kids
going to explain that in school
when people ask why their mommy
is on tv barely kissing Juan Valdez?
Sarah's best friend's mother just got
raped on Criminal minds last week.
A) rape is involuntary
and b) it's prime time.
- You are such an asshole.
- Baby
you're 30 minutes away
from getting it on
with a 19-year-old latin bullfighter
and I pass on hot pieces of ass
that throw themselves
at me all day every day
without so much
as a cupping of an ass cheek.
You know what? I'll tell you,
if you can get one of them
to fuck you on national
television, you have my blessing.
Ari, go back to work.
Baby, we agreed to suffer
through monogamy together.
If you love me,
you won't do it!
you will get the hell out of here.
Seriously, Ari,
you are pissing me off.
Go back to work.
Yeah, who's this?
The guy you smashed into last night.
Oh my God, I am so sorry
I gave you the wrong phone number.
- Yeah, you did.
- Oh, it was a total accident.
Another one?
How did you find my house?
- Star maps.
- Right.
So are you, like,
here to beat me up?
- No.
- 'Cause you do realize
it's a little nutty tracking
me down like this, right?
If you didn't look so harmless,
I'd be worried.
- I look harmless?
- Yeah, that's a good thing.
I'm in the business.
I manage Vincent Chase.
I'm not a crazy person.
I'm just a little pissed off.
I mean, you blew off the accident.
If I can just get your insurance info,
that'd be great.
Yeah.
Okay, come in.
Thank you.
I swear I didn't do it on purpose.
The phone is new and I'm
just totally number dyslexic.
3253, 2353...
my brain just can't
process the difference.
Well, I'm sorry
to just show up like this.
No, listen, I'm crazy
enough to do the same thing.
In high school
someone put gum on my locker once
and I spent three weeks trying
to track down who it was.
- What happened?
- I got my ass kicked by Jane Nevins,
the 300-lb resident school lunatic.
So should we do this?
- Yeah.
- Okay, here's mine.
There's my stuff right there.
So is your car totally screwed up?
Not too bad, actually.
Yours?
Completely.
I did something to the wheels.
You know, I guess
it's what I deserve.
I've been waiting
40 minutes for a cab
to take me to a meeting.
I am so late.
I can give you a lift.
Really?
you'd do that?
I probably should have asked
how far first.
Oh no, it's really close.
- No problem then.
- Okay, I'm gonna go grab my stuff.
This is nice.
We don't get too much alone time,
just you and me, bro.
So what do you want to do?
Well, we got no tv.
- Wanna talk?
- Sure.
I got nothin'.
Yeah, me neither.
You wanna smoke?
We promised Turtle we'd wait.
- I won't tell if you don't.
- Spark it up.
The little bastard took it all.
I was right to take it, 'cause you guys
cannot control yourselves.
When are you bringing it back?
Vince is bored.
I'll be home soon. Relax.
You'd better not smoke any of that
before you get back, Turtle.
Did you hear that?
Vince feels violated.
Oh, please. I would have
to nothing but stems
if I left it
with you two degenerates.
Excuse me.
Hey, I only have a few things.
Would you mind if I went ahead of you?
I'll call you back.
Sure, yeah, I'll let you go,
but if your boyfriend comes
running up here with 20 more items,
- I'm gonna be pissed.
- I don't have a boyfriend.
Then by all means.
Thanks.
Healthy living.
Me and my friend
are having a little midday fiesta.
You know what?
Me and my friends are having one too.
Maybe we should, combine parties.
- I don't think so.
- Oh, come on.
I guarantee our party
will be better than yours.
Oh, yeah? Why?
'cause it's at Vincent Chase's house.
Really?
- Javier.
- Yes?
Ari gold.
Do you know me?
Oh, yes yes,
I know of you.
I'd shake your hand,
but I just used my cocoa butter.
Are you interested
in representing me?
I may be.
I may be,
but right now
I'm interested
in talking to you
about your scene today.
Scene?
I have many scenes.
There's only one scene that
I wanna talk to you about.
- Which one is that?
- It's the one with Mrs. Gold.
- Mrs. Gold?
- Yeah, my wife.
- She plays Kendall Scott.
- Oh, Kendall Scott.
I'm sorry,
I only know character names.
I'm a method actor.
Well...
you're supposed
to kiss her on the mouth.
- Just acting.
- Don't.
The script says that I have to.
Look, Javier,
I can help you, okay?
You don't want to spend
the rest of your life
having fat middle-aged women
and odd homosexual men
getting off to your work, do you?
You have bigger dreams,
I'm sure, and let me tell you,
as anyone in this town can tell you,
I am a dreameaver, all right?
So you focus on what I'm saying
and I will have you kissing
Uggly Betty by Christmas,
but nobody gets to kiss my wife,
nobody but me.
Oh, this is nice.
I can get used to having
a personal driver.
I might have to take the
job just to keep the roads safe...
... with you driving, yes.
You know, you did stop short.
What are you talking about?
When you are the person
that crashes into another,
it's always your fault.
that's common knowledge.
Everybody knows that.
Yeah, I know...
but you did stop short.
A little bit.
But still, your fault.
So where am I taking you anyway?
I've got this meeting with a director
- for this movie I'm gonna do.
- Yeah? What movie?
- Brown-eyed girl.
- Okay, I've read that.
They sent it over
for Vince a ways back.
So what happened?
You didn't like it?
No, not for Vince.
Do you like it for me?
I mean, I don't know.
I read it for Vince.
Nice save.
Seriously, it was a long time ago.
I don't even remember specifics.
So is this it?
Can you please be honest and tell me
what you thought of the script?
What does it matter what I think?
Because now
I've gotta go into this meeting
and you're all in my head and...
just humor me.
I can take it.
Okay. All right, look, I didn't like it.
I mean, if it were just
a regular romantic comedy,
I'd go, "Okay, it's cute." but it's not.
It tries to be so much more.
When movies do that, I don't know,
it just... It pisses me off.
Look, the third act...
when it looks like
they're gonna get back
together and all of a sudden
she's taking off to start
an organic dog food company?
I mean, come on.
It just felt broad and manipulative
and just...
I don't know, I didn't buy it.
You really forgot the specifics, huh?
- Was that just way too honest?
- No no no.
No, I appreciate it.
And I really appreciate the ride.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So I guess
our insurance people will talk?
Yeah. I guess.
- It was nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you.
Good luck on your meeting.
Thank you.
So when do we get to smoke
some of this allegedly extinct weed?
When we get back to the house.
- Why can't we just smoke some now?
- 'Cause I promised my friends
I wouldn't smoke it without them.
That's kind of gay.
I thought you were gonna bring
two friends as hot as you.
Stop. She's cool.
- What's he saying about me up there?
- Nothing.
- Can we at least smell it?
- You can, 'cause you're hot.
Oh, eat me.
Not even if you
bathe yourself in butterscotch.
That smells good.
Just pass the bowl back
and let us take one hit.
Put the cap back on,
pass it up and shut up.
- Turtle!
- Stop sign!
Oh, shit.
Oh, great great.
Way to go, retard.
Hello, officer.
License, registration, please.
It's in here.
I'm gonna reach for it slow.
What's that smell?
And action!
- Miss Kendall.
- Come on, Julio,
you can't honestly call me that
with a straight face now that
you're all grown up.
I'm sorry.
You look amazing.
Miss Kendall,
you were my babysitter.
You're not a baby anymore.
And now that we're both adults,
I thought we could catch up
like adults.
- Miss Kendall...
- Julio,
what would you do to me
if I let you do anything
and if I promised
never to tell your Uncle Cuan?
Tell me, what would you do?
I would do...
- this.
- Cut!
What the fuck was that?
You're supposed to kiss her.
I thought it was
a little bit more romantic.
- It's not. Let's do it again.
- I'd rather not.
You'd rather not what?
I'd rather not kiss her.
What is the problem here?
I'm sorry, is it me?
Am I doing something wrong?
It's not you.
You're an incredible woman.
So what then?
It's him.
He threatened my career
and he promised me Ugly Betty.
I will be right back.
- You are interfering with my work.
- Baby, come on.
No matter what you say or do,
he's not gonna kiss you.
- Oh, really?
- No, it's not gonna happen.
You really think that?
I kissed him. It's done.
Let's shoot this.
You don't look like
you have glaucoma to me.
- What's he saying to him?
- I don't know,
but can he arrest all of us for this?
I'm telling him
he kidnapped us if he tries.
Officer, please.
We purchased that weed legally.
- We weren't gonna smoke it.
- Son, I don't want to hear
another syllable out of you
unless I ask you a question.
Now it says your truck
is registered to Vincent Chase.
Yeah, I'm sort of his driver.
Are you a fan?
And if I throw you in jail,
who's gonna drive your movie star down
- to bail you out?
- I don't know, sir, but please...
- Get down on your knees!
- What?
Down! Now!
- Flat on your stomach!
- Are you gonna shoot me right now?
No.
Drop it in the sewer.
Now get in your car
and get out of here.
I can go?
Better make it quick
before I change my mind.
Thank you, officer.
Thank you.
- What happened?
- Are you okay?
He made me throw the weed
down the sewer.
Bet your friends
are gonna be pissed.
Can I tape your mouth shut
if you're wrong?
What are you doing?
What?
I don't believe this guy.
What is he doing?
- How?
- Put it on the ledge.
Even I'm impressed.
Never tell an actress
you don't like her work, E.
Or an actor for that matter. It hurts.
I know.
I'm an idiot.
Don't feel too bad.
You were never gonna get her anyway.
Oh, thanks, Drama.
I feel much better now.
Anna.
Hey, Eric, it's Anna.
Listen,
I felt like we got cut off today.
Would you like to have dinner
with me tonight?
Yes, sure.
Sounds great.
- I can take a cab or...
- No, I'll pick you up.
- Great. How's 8:00?
- Perfect.
- All right, cool.
- I'll see you at 8:00.
Anna just asked me
to go out to dinner with her.
Nice!
- She asked you?
- Yeah.
Make sure you pay.
End this cycle of bitchdom.
- I'm home.
- Finally.
You'd better have something good.
Looks like someone found
some fresh meat at the market.
Guys, this is Laurie,
Morgan...
and yours, Drama.
E, I didn't know you were here,
or else I would have found a fourth.
You and Drama can fight it out for her.
- Thanks, Turtle.
- Hi there. Jonathan Chase.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Yeah, try taking that
and I'll break your fucking fingers.
It's 8:00. What are you doing in bed?
Long day.
I'm relaxing.
The kids eat?
- I made lasagna.
- You did?
It was stouffer's,
but I did the microwaving.
Look, about today...
forget today, all right?
Let's never talk about today again.
It's over and
I'm no longer mad...
You're no longer mad?
Well, I am mad,
you selfish prick.
- and I want an apology.
- No no, your little latin joyride
means me never having
to say I'm sorry.
- What, you're not gonna apologize?
- No, I'm not.
- Then how are we gonna get past this?
- I'm already past it,
unless you're gonna go
kiss another guy.
- then we're all good, all right?
- Well, I just may.
They asked me to be
a series regular on the show.
You're bluffing.
Am I?
I'm sorry, okay?
I get jealous.
You're possessive.
I don't want an apology for that.
What... for what then?
For...
for telling me that I am old
and that I wouldn't
photograph in high def.
It's a legitimate concern.
Look, I just didn't want
you doing it, all right?
I like the way things are.
I don't want you on television.
I don't want some
19-year-old kissing the lips
that I'm supposed
to be kissing, all right?
Listen, if you wanna go
and be a soap whore every day,
just do it knowing that you
make your husband miserable.
You think I want to do it, Ari?
I gave up acting to have a family
and I have never ever regretted it.
I like the way things are.
I just wanted to have
one day of stupid fun.
With Julio down at the schoolyard.
Well, if I'm so old and ugly,
why do you even care?
Well, some guys are into that.
I mean, you know...
Tell me that I am sexy, Ari.
Honey, you are...
the beautiful
mother of my children.
And I respect you.
You little slut!
I swear to god, my life...
I thought I was gonna die.
My god,
you're insane.
And thoroughly entertaining.
Thank you so much
for coming to dinner with me.
There's no arguments...
it's on me.
No shot.
I'm paying.
No no. We're gonna have
to fight it out when the bill comes.
- Oh, we will.
- Okay.
- So how was your meeting?
- Not good.
I told you,
you were in my head.
I'm sorry. I should
have kept my mouth shut.
No no. You know what? You were right.
I reread the script and I hate it.
You serious?
I knew I was justifying, though.
I mean,
it shoots in Italy for three months.
How great would that be?
But it's just not that good.
So what are you gonna do now?
I told my agent
to get me out of it.
Oh my God,
I feel terrible.
- This director's gonna kill me.
- No no.
No, you were right.
And good advice is hard to come by.
- Well...
- I actually wouldn't mind
picking your brain
for some more advice.
Sure.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hang on a second.
Hey, baby.
I'm probably gonna be
home in, like, two hours.
It's my boyfriend.
- That steak was amazing.
- Yeah, what do you season it with?
I'll never tell.
Oh, come on.
You'll tell me.
No, seriously, I won't.
It's unbelievable.
This shit just keeps going and going.
Yeah, so stop running your mouth
and keep it going.
No, I'm serious.
We've only had, like, an eighth,
- and it's still...
- Actually,
I might have come across another
secret stash while I was unpacking.
You're getting
sneakier and sneakier, Vin.
So what now, ladies?
Who's up for a little...
skinny dip?
- I'm in.
- All right.
- Anyone else?
- Be nice, Turtle.
I'm the only shot you got tonight.
- Really? I got a shot?
- No, not really.
- Hey, what up?
- Yo.
What's up is you missed the cable guy.
That's what's up.
- Oh, shit.
- Nice, Turtle.
- How was the big date?
- It wasn't a date. She has a boyfriend.
A boyfriend?
Why did she take you out to dinner?
She wanted some career advice.
She doesn't have a manager.
- She wants you to be her manager?
- Yep.
I told you you wouldn't fuck her.
All right, in the pool, ladies.
Let's go.
Yeah, baby.
Are you gonna tell me
what's on that steak?
We'll see.
I'll print out the recipe.
She wants you
to be her manager, huh?
Interesting.